You've learned a lot about thinking through algorithms with the seven steps,
你已经学到了很多关于通过算法思考的七个步骤、
the syntax and semantics of C and that
C 的语法和语义，以及
everything is a number principle and how it relates to types.
所有内容都是数字原理以及它与类型的关系。
We're going to take a moment to underscore
我们将花点时间
the importance of being specific when you write an algorithm.
强调在编写算法时保持具体性的重要性。
Humans can usually figure out vague instructions because they have common sense.
人类通常可以弄清楚模糊的指示，因为他们有常识。
However, computers do not have common sense and only do exactly what you tell them to.
但是，计算机没有常识，只能完全按照你的要求去做。
When you write an algorithm,
当你写一个算法时，
you have to carefully think through exactly what to
你必须仔细思考该怎么
do and be very specific as you write it down.
做，并且在写下来时要非常具体。
In the next course, we'll delve into turning your algorithm into code as well as
在接下来的课程中，我们将深入研究将你的算法转化为代码，以及
compiling and running the code and
编译和运行代码并
testing the code to be more confident that it's correct,
测试代码以使其更加确信其正确性，
then debugging it when something goes wrong.
然后在出现问题时对其进行调试。
However, before we get there,
但是，在我们开始之前，
we're going to wrap up this course with you writing an algorithm in
我们将结束这门课程，你用
English and having one of your fellow Coursera learners execute the algorithm.
英语写一个算法，然后让你的 Coursera 同学执行算法。
Of course you will also execute someone else's algorithm and peer review their work.
当然，你还将执行别人的算法，并对他们的工作进行同行评审。当@@
You want to be specific and clear when you do this so that
你这样做时，你需要具体而清晰，这样
whoever executes your algorithm knows exactly what to do.
无论谁执行你的算法，都确切地知道该怎么做。
To underscore the importance of being precise,
为了强调精确的重要性，
we're going to have a fun little demonstration of a vague algorithm.
我们将用一个有趣的小演示来演示一个模糊的算法。
Genevieve wrote me an algorithm to make a peanut butter and
吉纳维芙给我写了一个制作花生酱和
jelly sandwich and I've forgotten all of my common sense.
果冻三明治的算法，但我忘记了所有的常识。
So, I'm only willing to do exactly what she said.
所以，我只愿意照她说的去做。
All right, Genevieve.
好吧，吉纳维芙。
This is pretty basic.
这很基本。
I can't imagine what could go wrong.
我无法想象会出什么问题。
Okay.
好吧。
One, get out one piece of bread.
第一，拿出一块面包。
Okay, that seems hard to screw up.
好吧，这似乎很难搞砸了。
So far so good. Two, use a knife to put the peanut butter on it.
到目前为止还不错。第二，用刀在上面放花生酱。
Okay.
好吧。
This is trickier than you think.
这比你想象的要棘手。
I never knew that making a peanut butter sandwich was so difficult. All right.
我从来不知道做花生酱三明治这么难。好吧。
Three, get out another piece of bread.
第三，再拿出一块面包。
Okay.
好吧。
Four, use the knife to put the jelly on.
四，用刀把果冻放在上面。
Okay, she didn't really tell me where to put the jelly on.
好吧，她并没有真正告诉我该把果冻放在哪里。
But I guess if someone told me to like put my clothes on they mean to wear them.
但我猜如果有人叫我喜欢穿上我的衣服，他们就是要穿。
So, maybe she wants me to like wear that jelly. Yeah okay.
所以，也许她想让我喜欢戴那个果冻。是的还好。
Five, put the two pieces of bread together.
五，把两块面包放在一起。
All right, do you want me to bite the sandwich?
好吧，你想让我咬三明治吗？